http://www.snaptotes.com/pages/privacy-policy

Free Shipping on Orders Over $60
Need Help?
Ad Retargeting
Snaptotes shares your concerns about the protection of your personal information.  We collect certain information when you visit www.snaptotes.com (the “Site”) in order to improve your shopping experience and allow us to better communicate with you regarding our products and services.  This privacy policy (the “Policy”) is intended to assist you in understanding what information we gather when you visit the Site, how we use this information, and the safeguards we have in place to protect that information.
Using and submitting information to our site constitutes acceptance that we may collect, use and disclose the information described in the Policy in accordance with its terms.
Information We Collect Online
Snaptotes collects two types of information during your visits to our site.  The first type of information is personal information that you voluntarily provide to us as necessary to order products or to take advantage of the benefits provided by becoming a registered user.
You must provide your name, address, email address, phone numbers, billing address and shipping address when placing an order through the Site.  This information may be retained for use in future orders.  We also request payment information, such as a debit or credit card number, expiration date, and verification code.  We use your payment information only for a single transaction, and we do not retain it in our records.  As a result, you will need to re-enter this information each time you make a purchase with Snaptotes.
When signing up to become a registered user of Snaptote’s website, you must provide your name, phone number(s), email, password, secret question, and answer.  You may also provide a list of email addresses and contact information for use with your wish list, which will be stored in our records.  In addition you may provide us with information for use with our gift reminder service, including the occasion, the month and day of that occasion, and a name for the occasion.  You may also choose to upload digital photographs to our servers for use in the member’s area of the Site.
Snaptotes may administer online surveys to registered users in connection with the site, in which we ask you for demographic information and opinions.  We do not ask you for personally identifiable information as part of a survey.  We use the collected data on an aggregated basis to better understand the needs of all our customers.
The second type of collected information, while not personal information, is information about your shopping experience and purchases you make on the site.  When you visit the site, our web servers may automatically recognize certain non-personal identifiable information about you, such as your domain name, access provider, IP address, and browser language.  This site also uses a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer.RETURN TO TOP
How Collected Information is Used
The information collected when placing an order is only used for the purposes of processing, shipping, and completing that specific order.  As mentioned above, payment information is not stored anywhere in our system after its initial use to complete the transaction.  If a discrepancy occurs with your order, we may request your payment information again to make any necessary adjustments.
As a registered user, your email address may be used to notify you of new products, specials, or news about Snaptotes.  If at any time you do not wish to receive email from Snaptotes in the future, please unsubscribe using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email received from Snaptotes or simply email us at service@snaptotes.com and request to be removed from our email list.
The other information provided by you as a registered user, including email addresses for your wish list, contacts, photos and occasion dates, will only be stored for use at your direction.  Snaptotes will not contact the people in your wish list, unless those people elect to become registered members of the Site. Your contact information may also be used to contact you, when necessary.
The non-personal information from cookies is collected to aid Snaptotes in providing better customer service to you and improving the features of the Site; including determining which pages of the site have been visited, the order in which they were visited, and which links were “clicked.”  We also may use cookies and/or other tracking technologies to help us confirm your receipt of and response to our emails to provide you a more personalized experience.  Please note that certain pages of the site may not function properly if cookies are turned off.  Please consult your web browser’s help documentation for more information on how to turn you browser’s cookies on and off.
Snaptotes may share your information with selected third parties who provide services to us, including the processing of payments, monitoring site activity, and administering or responding to emails.  Such third parties may have access to, and may store and process your personal information to provide such services to us, and to you on our behalf.  Our service providers are not authorized to use your information for any purpose other than to provide contracted services.  We will not rent, sell, or exchange your email or mailing address and information about your transactions to any third parties.
In the unlikely event that Snaptotes is acquired by another company, or is subject to a change in control due to any merger, reorganization, or liquidation, Snaptote’s customer information will be among the transferred assets.
We reserve the right to disclose information about you as required by law, in response to legal process including law enforcement requests, and where needed to protect the safety, property, and legal rights of users of the site, or Snaptotes or third parties.RETURN TO TOP
Our Commitment to Security
In an effort to ensure that your transactions with Snaptotes are secure, we utilize secure servers and SSL encryption of transmissions, where appropriate.  We also use other technological and procedural safeguards, where appropriate, to maintain the security of our site.
We are not responsible for the practices employed by web sites linked to or from our web site nor the information or content contained therein.  Please remember that when you use a link to go from our web site to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites that have a link on our web site, is subject to that web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.RETURN TO TOP
Maintaining Your Personal Information
In efforts to enhance our service to you, we encourage you to regularly review and update your personal information.  You can access your personal information in our system by signing in and clicking on the “Members Area” button.RETURN TO TOP
Children's Privacy Protection
The Site is not designed for or intentionally targeted at children. It is not Snaptote’s policy to knowingly collect or maintain information about minors, and we ask that minors not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you may use this Site only in conjunction with a parent or legal guardian.RETURN TO TOP
Updating our Privacy Policy
Snaptotes reserves the right, at its discretion, to change this privacy policy at any time and without notice to you.  Please check this page periodically for changes to the Policy.  Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to this privacy policy will be considered your consent to those changes.RETURN TO TOP
Opting Out of our Site
If you feel this site is not following its stated information policy or you have questions or concerns about your privacy while using the site, please contact us at service@snaptotes.com.RETURN TO TOP
Disclaimer
You acknowledge that electronic communications, databases and web sites are subject to errors, malfunctions, tampering and break-ins, or that use thereof may result in damages to the user's systems or operations. While Snaptotes implements reasonable precautions to attempt to prevent such occurrences, the user further acknowledges that Snaptotes does not guarantee such events will not take place and that Snaptotes will not be held liable for any such occurrences. The user shall be solely responsible for ensuring any information or content downloaded from this web site or any other web site accessed from Snaptote’s web site does not contain any virus or other computer software code or subroutine designed to disable, erase, impair or otherwise damage its systems, software or data. The user shall indemnify, defend and hold Snaptotes or its subsidiaries harmless from any liability, claim, cost or damage arising out of any third-party claim or suit caused by such virus or code or subroutine.RETURN TO TOP
Effective Date
This privacy policy is effective May 21, 2008.RETURN TO TOP
Contacting Snaptotes®
Should you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at customerservice@ericscott.com or toll free at 1.800.707.3186, 8:00 am to 4:30 pm CST, Monday - Friday.RETURN TO TOP
Ad Retargeting
Snaptotes works with AdRoll retargeting, who uses technology including web beacons and cookies to collect data about our website usage and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. Data recorded through the use of this technology is aggregated and shared with us. No personally identifiable information about you is collected or shared by AdRoll with Snaptotes. You can opt-out of AdRoll and their partners by visiting this link. See more at: http://www.mobile-rhino.com/ourpolicy.php#sthash.dPdX2FvD.dpufRETURN TO TOP
Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection
Are you sure you want to delete all item ?
Yes Clear
Cancel
